design3edge.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Design3edge

Privacy Policy for www.design3edge.com

At www.design3edge.com, the privacy of our visitors is important to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.design3edge.com and how it is used.

**Log Files**  
Like many other web sites, www.design3edge.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies**  
www.design3edge.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Ad Networks**  
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies on our site.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

We use the following ad networks:

1\. Google  
Informations about Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie:  
– Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.  
– Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to www.design3edge.com users based on their visit to www.design3edge.com site and other sites on the Internet.  
– Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

2\. Advertising.com  
Informations about AOL Advertising privacy policy – [read here](http://advertising.aol.com/privacy).

3\. BuyAds  
Informations about BuyAds privacy policy – [read here](https://www.buyads.com/privacy).

3\. BuySellAds  
Informations about BuySellAds privacy policy – [read here](http://buysellads.com/about/privacy).

Links to external sites  
This site contains links to other sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browser’s respective websites.

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.design3edge.com/contact-us/).
